If you're feeling dejected, you're feeling weak, you're feeling like there's no way to fight,
then you need to stick around and watch this little supercut of Venezuelans standing on business saying we are not them ones.
We are the twos, the threes and the fours.
And I'm going to say it in criollo, so that you have to be careful with what you're going to do in our country,
because here we are the real guerreras, the blood of the liberator that runs through the veins,
and that we are not going to let you get wrong with us, because if something we know is to fight in the streets,
so don't let you get wrong, Maria Corina, and there's no Nobel Prize for you, that's a lie.
La paz está aquí, en el pueblo de Nicolás Maduro, en el pueblo de Chávez.
Estamos conmemorando 26 años de nuestra constitución.
La constitución que reconoce a los afrodescendientes, a la textodiversidad, a las mujeres, le da participación.
A los pueblos indígenas le ha dado un capítulo especial.
Es Chávez quien le da el protagonismo a ese pueblo venezolano,
porque ya que la constitución que teníamos no era el pueblo venezolano protagonista, ni tenía derecho, ni voto, ni voto.
Los días contados lo tiene el imperio norteamericano, nuestro presidente no.
Donald Trump, no te equivoques, que Venezuela camina, camina y seguiremos lucha y batalla.
Estamos unidos en esta situación que tenemos, y estamos alegres por la unidad, o sea, porque estamos unidos.
Pero también estamos en esa unión para ir también para defender nuestra patria, defenderla y defender nuestra riqueza.
Y hoy, nuestros soldados nunca irán a nuestra vida.
Nosotros realmente lucharemos hasta el último hombre, hasta el último mujer, hasta el último joven, hasta el último joven.
Y sabemos que tenemos la solidaridad de los pueblos del mundo en esta lucha.
So, think twice before you come and fade Venezuela and Colombia.
Across all the people of Latin America, I tell them, let's unite against this aggression of the empire,
that doesn't want to die, doesn't want to accept that it doesn't have the same strength as before.
We need to tell everybody, I want to tell all my friends, all my brothers from the Latin American continent,
from the Abia Yala, we are stronger and united.
They will never, never win.
Support a real one.